<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MyRedditApplication</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="write_topic">write a topic...</string>

    <string name="MMA_fighter">An MMA fighter appearing on Survivor Romania loses a competition then she breaks her teammates nose</string>
    <string name="Trump">Russia is working to get Trump reelected, intelligence officials tell House lawmakers in briefing that angers the president</string>
    <string name="moustache">TIL Salvador Dali once conned Yoko Ono out of $10,000 by sending her a piece of dried grass instead of a hair from his moustache</string>
    <string name="histories">Forcing us to get consent before selling browser histories violates our free speech, US ISPs claim</string>
    <string name="alone">Why do you like to be alone?</string>
    <string name="WSOP">Join the official WSOP online poker game and enjoy monthly updates, exciting tournaments and daily live events</string>
    <string name="poker"> Test your poker skills with the best online poker experience including Texas Hold’em tables, high-stakes tournaments and daily Jackpots!</string>
    <string name="Towel">Towel animal left by the hotel staff</string>
    <string name="boomers">Did you know baby boomers share almost 7x as much disinformation on social media than other adults?</string>
    <string name="CPR">CPR machine being used in a real situation in Italy</string>


    <string name="Youth">Youth behavior trends in the United States, 9th grade, 14-15 years old [OC]OC</string>
    <string name="TIFU">TIFU by insulting a guys micropenis and ruining the hookupM</string>
    <string name="term">“looking for something long term” no shit</string>
    <string name="marathon">It\'s a marathon, not a sprint</string>
    <string name="Reddit">Get Reddit Premium for the finest Reddit experience, including ads-free browsing and 700 Coins every month</string>
    <string name="point">The point of view really matters</string>
    <string name="Sunday"> The Sunday Bunnies</string>
    <string name="Sanders">Sanders reveals free childcare plan for preschoolers</string>
    <string name="Grocery">Grocery stores need a website/app that allows shoppers to input their list and it outputs a map to follow in the store that eliminates back tracking.</string>
    <string name="Airport">DFW Airport added a gaming lounge so you can game while you wait for your plane</string>
</resources>
